"lang"
{
	"Language" "English"
	"Tokens"
	{
		// Auto messages
		"Phone_Auto_SafeZone_UpAhead"			"The SafeZone has been located! Let's clear it out and group up!"

		// These are split
		"Phone_Auto_PanicZombieAmount_01"			"There are"
		"Phone_Auto_PanicZombieAmount_02"			"Zombies spotted in the area."

		//====================================================
		// Shared
		"Phone_Shared_Zombies"					"Zombies"
		"Phone_Shared_Dial"						"Dial"

		"Phone_Shared_Day_0"					"Sunday"
		"Phone_Shared_Day_1"					"Monday"
		"Phone_Shared_Day_2"					"Tuesday"
		"Phone_Shared_Day_3"					"Wednesday"
		"Phone_Shared_Day_4"					"Thursday"
		"Phone_Shared_Day_5"					"Friday"
		"Phone_Shared_Day_6"					"Saturday"

		"Phone_Shared_Month_0"					"January"
		"Phone_Shared_Month_1"					"Febuary"
		"Phone_Shared_Month_2"					"March"
		"Phone_Shared_Month_3"					"April"
		"Phone_Shared_Month_4"					"May"
		"Phone_Shared_Month_5"					"June"
		"Phone_Shared_Month_6"					"July"
		"Phone_Shared_Month_7"					"August"
		"Phone_Shared_Month_8"					"September"
		"Phone_Shared_Month_9"					"October"
		"Phone_Shared_Month_10"					"November"
		"Phone_Shared_Month_11"					"December"

		// Date format
		// %month% -- ex; July
		// %day% -- ex; Sunday
		// %day_num% -- ex; 16
		// %day_frmt% -- ex; 16th
		"Phone_Shared_FormatDate"				"%day%, %month% %day_frmt%"

		// Translatable formats
		"Phone_Shared_Format_Day_st"			"st"
		"Phone_Shared_Format_Day_nd"			"nd"
		"Phone_Shared_Format_Day_rd"			"rd"
		"Phone_Shared_Format_Day_th"			"th"

		// Dumb easter-egg, try to find it!
		"Phone_EasterEgg_01_GameOver"			"Game Over"
		"Phone_EasterEgg_01_TapToStart"			"Tap to Start"

		// Escape
		"Phone_Escape_Message"					"Message"
		"Phone_Escape_ObjDist"					"Objective Distance"

		// Flatline
		"Phone_Flatline_Shop"					"Open Shop"
		"Phone_Flatline_Wave"					"Wave"
		"Phone_Flatline_Cash"					"Cash"
		"Phone_Flatline_BeginsIn"				"begins in"
		"Phone_Flatline_Seconds"				"seconds"

		// Extraction
		"Phone_Extraction_NoSignal"				"No GPS signal..."
		"Phone_Extraction_Destination"			"You have reached your destination."

		// Hunted
		"Phone_Hunted_SearchDevices"			"Searching For Devices..."
		"Phone_Hunted_NoDevices"				"No Devices Found..."
		"Phone_Hunted_DeviceList"				"Device List"
		"Phone_Hunted_AttempConnect"			"Attempting to Connect..."

		//====================================================

		"Phone_Survivor_Eugene"		"Eugene"
		"Phone_Survivor_Marcus"		"Marcus"
		"Phone_Survivor_Nick"		"Nicholas"
		"Phone_Survivor_Tony"		"Tony"
		"Phone_Survivor_Jessica"	"Jessica"
		"Phone_Survivor_Nicole"		"Nicole"
		"Phone_Survivor_Ryan"		"Ryan"
		"Phone_Survivor_Lawrence"	"Lawrence"
		"Phone_Survivor_Curtis"		"Curtis"
		"Phone_Survivor_Manuel"		"Manuel"
		"Phone_Survivor_Mia"		"Mia"
		"Phone_Survivor_Yumi"		"Yumi"
		"Phone_Survivor_Mike"		"Mike"
		"Phone_Survivor_Survivor"	"Survivor"

		//====================================================

		// Biotec
		"VSCRIPT_Biotec_00"				"The basement is locked. We'll need to find keys."
		"VSCRIPT_Biotec_01"				"I've reset the generator, this should take care of the lockdown. Let's keep moving!"
		"VSCRIPT_Biotec_02"				"I found keys. These may be useful."
		"VSCRIPT_Biotec_03"				"I found a blue keycard. This will help us get past blue keycard scanners."
		"VSCRIPT_Biotec_04"				"The building is under lockdown and security shutters are blocking our way. We need to find a way to end the lockdown."
		"VSCRIPT_Biotec_05"				"I found keys. Maybe these can unlock the basement."
		"VSCRIPT_Biotec_06"				"I found a blue keycard. This should open the security doors in the lobby."
		"VSCRIPT_Biotec_07"				"There's a blue keycard scanner next to the automated doors in the lobby. We'll need a blue keycard to get through."
		"VSCRIPT_Biotec_08"				"There's a red keycard scanner in the yellow hallway. Let's search for a red keycard in the nearby offices."
		"VSCRIPT_Biotec_09"				"Damn, this keycard scanner is busted. The schematics showed another way in up on the roof."
		"VSCRIPT_Biotec_10"				"I've disengaged the first cold storage lab security button. We'll need to find the other security station and disable the second lock."
		"VSCRIPT_Biotec_11"				"Both security locks disabled, the cold storage lab should be unlocked now."
		"VSCRIPT_Biotec_12"				"I've found and obtained the experimental vaccine! We need to get to the roof and to signal the chopper."
		"VSCRIPT_Biotec_13"				"This is NOT good. The security system detected a breach and the labs are set to self destruct soon. We must reach the roof and leave now!"
		"VSCRIPT_Biotec_14"				"I found a keycode. It's 0451."
		"VSCRIPT_Biotec_15"				"I found a keycode. It's 1998."
		"VSCRIPT_Biotec_16"				"There's a keypad blocking the entrance. Check the surrounding labs for the code, it may be written down on a post-it stuck on a monitor."
		"VSCRIPT_Biotec_17"				"I found a red keycard. We can use this on red keycard scanners."
		"VSCRIPT_Biotec_18"				"I found a red keycard. Now we can open that door in the yellow hall."
		"VSCRIPT_Biotec_19"				"The laboratory is open. We might find what we came for in these labs."
		"VSCRIPT_Biotec_20"				"We've found an underground lab. This place has the best chance of having a working vaccine."
		"VSCRIPT_Biotec_21"				"The doors to cold storage are locked. It looks like it can be unlocked by controls in the security stations."
		"VSCRIPT_Biotec_22"				"I've signalled the chopper. It should be here soon."
		"VSCRIPT_Biotec_23"				"The pilot won't land until we've initiated the lockdown from the roof's security station and cleared all infected near the helipad."
		"VSCRIPT_Biotec_24"				"Lockdown initiated. Everyone needs to get to the roof immediately! In 30 seconds the shutters will close."
		"VSCRIPT_Biotec_25"				"All zombies down. Lets get out of here!"
		"VSCRIPT_Biotec_26"				"Great, we've made it to the labs. Must find a way into their secure cold storage lab further in."
		"VSCRIPT_Biotec_27"				"I've unlocked the basement. Let's look for a way to end the lockdown in here."
		"VSCRIPT_Biotec_28"				"The blue keycard doors in the lobby are unlocked now. Let's keep moving."
		"VSCRIPT_Biotec_29"				"This lab is full of toxic looking gas. Better stay out unless we have a gasmask."
		"VSCRIPT_Biotec_30"				"Get into the chopper now! We're leaving in 30 seconds"
		"VSCRIPT_Biotec_31"				"These labs look damaged. We should put on gas masks before continuing."
		"VSCRIPT_Biotec_Init"			"We made it to Biotec. Hopefully we'll find something... anything, to help fight the zombie virus."

		"AS_Biotec_TimeRunningOut"		"Time is running out! We need to get out of here before it blows!"

		// Barlowesquare
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_Init"	"This whole city is not safe, we need to get the hell out of here."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_00"		"Damn, we need to get the hell out of here and the door is locked. There has to be a set of keys around here somewhere."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_01"		"Okay so now that we have the keys, let's get out of here."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_02"		"Isn't Chuck's gun store on the corner of Burough and Kellogg Street? Because we could really use the extra supplies."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_03"		"It looks like all of our routes are blocked off. Let's try and cut through that apartment building over there."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_04"		"Chuck's is just around the corner now, let's keep going!"
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_05"		"Well we made it. Now grab as much weapons and ammo as you can, otherwise we might as well be sitting ducks."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_06"		"I recall hearing that the military was holding down Barlowe Square, just south of the Cinema. It's our best bet."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_07"		"Navigating the streets is not the best idea. But I don't see any other option right now. Let's just keep going."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_08"		"Crap, this way is blocked off! But that's the back of Goldie's Cinema. Let's try to get around and see what we find."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_09"		"This looks like the safest route, but it's locked. We need to find something that would make easy work of this chain."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_10"		"Let's scavenge the City Surplus. The Gas Station is worth checking out too, hopefully we find a set of boltcutters."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_11"		"These boltcutters should do the job! Let's head on through Goldie's Cinema and get to Barlowe Square."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_12"		"Great, we made it in! Replenish any supplies while we have the chance, then we'll make our way through."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_13"		"Fuck, looks like the military abandoned their post.. or worse. Surely they had some form of communication!"
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_14"		"Bingo! I've found a radio. Hopefully it still operational! Let's call for some help!"
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_15"		"Somebody answered! They're telling us to find a safe location and hold out. The Bank has to be the most secure!"
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_16"		"So the Bank is in the North East. Let's pick up the pace! It's close to the Auto Detailing garage we passed earlier."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_17"		"We need to take care of all the threats inside first, then secure the entrances. Just hope that rescue arrives soon."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_18"		"Dammit, I see no way to avoid these flames. We need a Fire Extinguisher, then we can push through."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_19"		"That Extinguisher might come in handy later on, better safe than sorry."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_20"		"What the hell is that alarm?! If we don't find and shut that shit off now, every zombie in the city is going to come knocking!"
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_21"		"There's no way in hell they didn't hear that, we disabled it too late. Prepare for a fight, they'll be coming."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_22"		"There's a horde approaching. Quickly! Barricade all we can, stay put and stay calm, help is on the way!"
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_23"		"Alright! The cavalry has arrived, let's get to the truck! What a fucking mess."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_24"		"Hurry to the truck! They won't hang around for long! Do, not, die."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_25"		"I knew the military wouldn't be here. Let's just get far away from this city. We're going to need supplies though, let's hit Chuck's gun store."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_26"		"The streets look rough, but we'll have to make our way through. Let's hope we can bypass some of the checkpoints."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_27"		"The road is blocked. We should be able to make our way through to Chucks. Let's try the Surplus or those apartments."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_28"		"Chuck's gun store is just around the corner! Let's not slow down now, we're almost there!"
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_29"		"Well we made it in one piece! Now let's reap the reward, stock up on any weapons and ammo you can find!"
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_30"		"Once we're stocked up, I think a good option for us would be the subway. It's not far from here."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_31"		"It's locked down, typical. Check the maintenance area, maybe there is a better way to get inside."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_32"		"Damn! This maintenance tunnel would be our best entrance into the subway, but it's locked..."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_33"		"I'm pretty sure a regular at Larry's diner works here, he lives above Ray's Tavern. Let's loot his apartment for a set of keys."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_34"		"These apartments are locked too, there has to be another way inside. Let's not give up."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_35"		"I'm not sure which room is his, search them all for any keys. They must be around here somewhere."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_36"		"These must be the keys! Let's head back to the maintenance area and get out of here, finally."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_37"		"Great, we're in. Let's head down into the subway and get one of those things rolling."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_38"		"Let's check the controller office and open these damn shutters. Then we can board one of the trains!"
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_39"		"We have to turn on the generators to get this place up and running. Let's take a look around, it seems like there is a lot."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_40"		"Oh shit! It's opening the front gates! They're getting in and we still have more to activate, get these shutters moving!"
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_41"		"That seems to have done the trick, at least they're moving! Let's head on down, board a train and escape from this mess!"
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_42"		"C'mon! Get on the train ASAP! It's going to leave very soon!"
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_43"		"We need to find an Extinguisher to put out this fire."

		// Barlowesquare (The workshop version, reads this)
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_00_PARTA"		"Damn, we need to get the hell out of here and the door is locked. There has to be a set of keys around here somewhere."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_01_PARTA"		"The streets look rough, but we'll have to make our way through. Let's hope we can bypass some of the checkpoints."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_02_PARTA"		"The military camp looks overrun, and I don't think that's a good thing..."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_03_PARTA"		"And it looks like all of our routes are blocked off. Let's hope the backdoor to the cinema isn't locked up."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_04_PARTA"		"Goldie's Cinema is still open, thank god! let's keep going!"
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_05_PARTA"		"Navigating the streets is not the best idea. But I don't see any other option right now. Let's just keep going."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_06_PARTA"		"I recall hearing that the military was holding down Barlowe Square, just south of the Cinema. It's our best bet."

		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_PARTB_InitStart"						"Let's get out of the bank, I don't think help will come if we simply stay here..."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_PARTB_Escape_A"						"C'mon! Get on the train ASAP! It's going to leave very soon!"
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_PARTB_Escape_B"						"Hurry to the truck! They won't hang around for long! Do, not, die."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_PARTB_RadioIsSuccess"				"The military is on it's way! Let's hold out until they arrive!"
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_PARTB_RadioIsSuccess_B"				"Alright! The cavalry has arrived, let's get to the truck! What a fucking mess."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_PARTB_LastEvent"						"Well, it looks like it's either the subway, or call for help route..."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_PARTB_InsideSubway"					"Let's check the controller office! It's our best bet at this point."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_PARTB_FindKeys"						"I'm not sure which apartment is his, search them all for any keys."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_PARTB_ToApartments"					"Let's head through the apartments, maybe we can find a way to Chucks gunstore through it."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_PARTB_AtCitSurplus"					"Let's scavenge the City Surplus. The Gas Station is worth checking out too, if it's not blocked off."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_PARTB_AtGunStore"					"Well we made it. Now grab as much weapons and ammo as you can, otherwise we might as well be sitting ducks."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_PARTB_ToGasStation"					"Chuck's gun store is just around the corner! Let's not slow down now, we're almost there!"
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_PARTB_AtSubway"						"It's locked down, typical. Check the maintenance area, maybe there is a better way to get inside."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_PARTB_OnLeaveBank"					"This looks like the safest route to City Surplus. But don't let your guard down, even if it looks safe!"
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_PARTB_MainGateOpens"					"Oh shit! It's opening the front gates! They're getting in and we still have more to activate, get these shutters moving!"
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_PARTB_SubwayEventBegins"				"We have to turn on the generators to get this place up and running. Let's take a look around, it seems like there is a lot."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_PARTB_EventSubwayGates"				"That seems to have done the trick! Let's head back,"
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_PARTB_EventSubwayGates_PartA"		"activate the shutters and board the train"
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_PARTB_EventSubwayGates_PartB"		"call for help and get out of here"
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_PARTB_TriggerAtMaintenance"			"Damn! This maintenance tunnel would be our best entrance into the subway, but it's locked..."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_PARTB_TriggerAtMaintenance_2"		"I'm pretty sure a regular at Larry's diner works here, he lives above Ray's Tavern. Let's loot his apartment for a set of keys."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_PARTB_EventDoorShaft"				"Great, we're in. Let's head down into the subway and get one of those things rolling."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_PARTB_EventPickupApartmentKeys"		"These must be the keys! Let's head back to the maintenance area and get out of here, finally."

		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_BurnBlockHas"	"Let's use that Extinguisher to put out this fire."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_BurnBlock"		"We need to find an Extinguisher to put out this fire."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_Keyes"			"I found some keys, hopefully these will come in handy."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_Exting_A"		"Someone had an Extinguisher on them earlier, we could use that right about now."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_Exting_B"		"Let's use the Extinguisher to get into the bank ASAP!"
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_Exting_Pickup"	"That Extinguisher might come in handy later on, better safe than sorry."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_BankAlarm"		"SHIT! The bank alarm went off! Every damn undead freak is on their way here now!"
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_BankTrig"		"Damn, the ways out of here is blocked! Let's hope we can find a way out through the bank!"
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_BankBase"		"The security doors are shut tight! We need to find the override somewhere!"
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_KeyCard"			"I found the keycard for the security room!"
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_KeyCardNotify"	"We gotta find something, a card or something to get out of here! and QUICK!"
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_GateProblem"		"Ah shit. The gate is having problems opening! We need to hold out until it's fully opened!"
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_GateOpen"		"It's fully opened! Let's head to the vault!"
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_FireIsOut"		"The fire has been put out!, let's head inside!"
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_RadioIsDead"		"It's no use, the battery is dead... We have to find another way out of here."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_RadioIsBroken"	"It's no use, it's broken..."
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_CinemaLock"		"We can't go around and the cinema is locked up tight. We need something to cut through the chains and pass through the Cinema."

		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_Generators"		"We have to turn on the generators to get this place up and running. Let's take a look around, it seems like there is a lot."

		// Because of Vscript, this was split into 2.
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_Generator_00"		"Let's keep looking guys, there are"
		"VSCRIPT_BarloweSquare_Generator_01"		"generators left for us to find and activate!"

		"AS_BarloweSquare_ToApartments_A"				"Let's head through the apartments, maybe we can find a way through it."
		"AS_BarloweSquare_ToApartments_B"				"The apartments are blocked off, maybe we can find a way that alley over there."

		// Camp Whitner
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_StormComing"				"Damn, looks like a storm is approaching..."
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_KeysFound"					"You found the Dmitry's keys nice work, unlock the green metal door by the main building and get the power back up."
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_KeyCardFound_Red"			"The red keycard will get you into the living quarters on the northeast side of the campgrounds, head on over when you are done looting."
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_RedKeyCard_Toss"			"The red keycard is useless now, you can discard it."
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_KeyCardFound_Blue"			"When you are ready you can turn on the blue emergency backup generator, I don't know how this is going to go so be ready for anything."
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_BlueKeyCard_Toss"			"The blue keycard is useless now, you can discard it."
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_DoorBlocked"				"Won't budge, something must be blocking it from the other side..."
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_StayClear"					"Stay clear of the landing spot dumbass, this ain't no video game!"
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_EventMapStart"				"Damn, there is no getting though all this wreckage. That gate back up the road was open, we should go check it out."
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_EventHelpMe"				"Is anyone there? Hello? Please I need help! If you are receiving this message please respond!"
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_EventHelpMeFollow"			"Thank God! Listen, my name is Jason and I'm barricaded up in this camp. This guy Sebastian, he... he's killed so many..."
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_EventHelpMeFollowUp"		"The one's that refused to drink the punch, he methodically hunted down and shot like dogs..."
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_EventHelpMeFollowUp2"		"I managed to stay hidden, but I don't know how long my luck will last, please hurry!"
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_EventEnterMain"			"This isn't going to be easy, the first thing you need to do is find Dmitry the maintenance guy's key ring."
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_EventEnterMainDelayed"		"Dmitry was a bit of a drunk and was always leaving his keys lying around, check outside around the main building where you entered."
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_EventStillNoKeys"			"Still no luck finding the keys huh? Check around the two decks and gazebos, I often found him passed out around there at the end of his shift."
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_MainPowerOn"				"Good job! Looks like most of the power is restored all over the camp, except for the dorms but we'll worry about that later. Get inside the lobby quick!"
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_OfficeSearch"				"You have to find a red keycard which will grant access to the dorms on the other side of the camp. Grab whatever else you can find that might help."
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_EventStartDorms"			"There probably isn't much left in the armory but you should grab whatever there is, I got a feeling you're probably going to need it..."
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_EventDiscoverDorms"		"There should be a blue keycard somewhere inside either one of the dorms or in one of the two bath houses, probably on a dresser or something."
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_EventDiscoverDorms2"		"This is probably going to draw a lot of unwanted attention, make sure you are ready before you start up the generator."
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_DormPowerButtonPressed"	"SHIT! the backup generator is not charged up enough, you're going to have to hold out a bit until it can handle the load."
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_BlueReaderFix"				"OK! The card reader appears to be back online, use the blue keycard and get the hell out of there!"
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_MaintenenceRoom"			"Dmitry's workshop is on the left, you should find something that can cut the locks off the gates, probably a boltcutter."
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_BreakDoor"					"You should be able to use that fire axe to break through the door."
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_ShootingRange"				"Dmitry's boltcutters should make quick of any padlocked gates..."
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_BreakerKitchen"			"Looks like the power surge tripped the breaker in the kitchen. Make your way up the hill back behind the main building and cut the lock to the cage there."
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_EscapeRoof"				"Before we continue we should see if this radio is working and try and reach someone."
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_CallHelp"					"I've set the radio to repeatedly send out an sos, we should stay here for a while and wait for a response before we move on."
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_CallHelp2"					"I've got visual on some survivors but there's no place to land. Try and head further north and I'll see if I can find a place to land."
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_PowerReturn"				"OK the power is restored to the kitchen, get up to the roof now and have a look around. You should be able to try and signal for help."
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_JumpyRoof"					"Jump through the window and break through those boards, I'm straight ahead barricaded up in the attic. I... it doesn't matter."
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_CodeToFreedom"				"Ok we got the code, 5430. Thanks for all your help Jason, we'll make sure Sebastian pays for all the lives he's ruined."
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_NothingCanDo"				"There's nothing we can do for him, it's only a matter of time before he turns. Time for a little revenge, let's get to the compound."
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_CompoundEnter"				"I don't like this... It's quiet, too damn quiet. Let's have a look around, I got the feeling Sebastian has us right where he wants us..."
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_SebasWillDie"				"Looks like Sebastian was up to more than just preaching to his followers. Drug and weapon trafficking, as if I needed another reason to hate this prick."
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_ItsATrap"					"It's a trap, there is no way out, we are completely screwed! Take as many of em out as you can, if I die today I'm going down standing up!"
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_HordeTime"					"The garage doors are opening! We gotta find a way out, there must be a switch or something hurry up and find it!"
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_SebasIsDead"				"Why am I not surprised, the bastard took the easy way out.  Good riddance..."
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_RipYourWall"				"Shit the wall has dynamite but has not been lit! Find a way to ignite the fuse or we're done for!"
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_PoliceChatter"				"I think I hear police chatter, let's keep moving there has to be a way out of here."
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_BreakTrough"				"What if we break the lamp next to the fuse, that might do the trick!"
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_PoliceChoppa"				"It's that police chopper! RUN RUN RUN! They have to see us!"
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_ChoppaLand"				"I think he's trying to land on top of that train car! Get up there and be ready but give him some room to land!"
		"VSCRIPT_CampWhitner_GetYoAssInHere"			"This shit is insane!!! Hurry the hell up and get in before I change my mind!!!"

		// Harvest
		"VSCRIPT_Harvest_MainPower"					"The main power is out. We should locate the circuit breaker and restore power to the house."
		"VSCRIPT_Harvest_KeyBreaker"				"Locked. The breaker is probably inside, we need to find the keys that open it."
		"VSCRIPT_Harvest_KeysLocated"				"Found the keys, we can access the circuit breaker now."
		"VSCRIPT_Harvest_SecurityLock"				"The house alarm is attracting all the zombies! We have to hold them off until the card reader has been rebooted!"
		"VSCRIPT_Harvest_KeyCardFound"				"Found a keycard. This should come in handy."
		"VSCRIPT_Harvest_KeyCardReader"				"The keycard reader is back up get that door open!"
		"VSCRIPT_Harvest_DrDrugsInDaHouse"			"This place is an illegal drug operation... Better keep looking around and see what else there is."
		"VSCRIPT_Harvest_PlungerFound"				"The wall is rigged with explosives. That's our way out but the plunger seems to be missing the handle, gotta find it."
		"VSCRIPT_Harvest_WallGoBoom"				"The fuse is set, everyone better stand clear!!!"
		"VSCRIPT_Harvest_PlungerUsed"				"We've broken through the wall, let's see where this leads us."
		"VSCRIPT_Harvest_GenerateHate"				"The generator powering the floodlights is off, but first we need to find a way to call for help.  Maybe we should look around the other buildings outside."
		"VSCRIPT_Harvest_BoltCutters"				"Found some boltcutters, these might come in handy."
		"VSCRIPT_Harvest_ChickenCoop"				"The chicken coop doors are padlocked, did anyone find something we can cut the lock off with?"
		"VSCRIPT_Harvest_RadioEscape"				"Ok we've called for help and they are on the way, get that generator in the barn started so they see the lights and don't pass us by!"
		"VSCRIPT_Harvest_FloodLights"				"The floodlights are on but this generator doesn't sound so good.  We'll have to restart it if it dies on us."
		"VSCRIPT_Harvest_GeneratorHatesYou"			"The generator turned off, get it up and running again before the EVAC gets here!!!"
		"VSCRIPT_Harvest_EVACSoonBaby"				"The EVAC will be here in less then a minute, make sure the floodlights are on!!!"
		"VSCRIPT_Harvest_EVACIsHere"				"We did it, I see the EVAC approaching, now let's get to the truck!!!"
		"VSCRIPT_Harvest_EVACGoAway"				"We missed the EVAC... That's it, we're done for..."

		// Montclair
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_LeftInAHurry"				"Whoever lives here left in a hurry, we should look around and grab anything useful before we leave."
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_PowerIsOut"					"Looks like some breakers might be tripped, why would they flip only some of them? Let's make sure we're ready before we turn the power back on."
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_CallForExtraction"			"I've called for an extraction, let's wait and see if anyone responds."
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_PilotSaysNoToYou"			"Pilot: Too many zombies in the area and I don't see a clear place to land. The code to the armory is 8253, good luck!"
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_FlipDaSwitch"				"Flipped the breaker, maybe something important has power now. SHIT! The house alarm system was also turned on!"
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_FlipDaSwitch2"				"Flipped the breaker, maybe something important has power now. SHIT! The house alarm system is on but some systems are malfunctioning!"
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_PlantationYay"				"Looks like all systems are back up in the plantation!"
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_SewersWithGas"				"Oh... Another sewer... Great... On a positive note, at least this one isn't full of lethal gas."
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_MazeHunt4Card"				"Probably easy to get turned around in here, gotta find that key card though..."
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_ReachFinaleYay"				"It's the gas station we saw near the park, so this was the way in. Hopefully there's something useful in here, looked pretty secure from the outside."
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_CutGate"						"This is our way out of here, should wait until our EVAC arrives before we cut the lock..."
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_CutLock"						"Our ride is here! Cut the lock and let's get the hell out of here!!!"
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_DiscoverRadio"				"A radio we can use to call for help. This will probably draw a lot of attention, when ready go ahead and use it but be ready for one hell of a fight."
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_RadioSuccess"				"We hear you loud and clear and are in route. ETA 3 minutes, make sure there's a safe place for us to land."
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_RadioSuccess2"				"We hear you loud and clear and are in route. ETA 3 minutes, we'll back right up to the gate outside the gas station so be ready."
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_CallForHelp"					"Called for extraction, hopefully someone is listening on the other end. We have to wait for a response it's our only hope for escape!"
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_FoundTheKeys"				"Found a set of keys..."
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_GardenMazeTime"				"The garden maze behind the house looks like we need to enter a code to open the gate."
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_GeneratorStarts"				"Got 1 generator started, one more to go."
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_GeneratorStarts2"			"Right that's both generators running, looks like power is restored."

		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_OBJ_00"				"Should check all the houses for supplies and useful items on the way to the heart of the city."
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_OBJ_01"				"Found a fire extinguisher, this might come in handy."
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_OBJ_02"				"No way to get through this without a fire extinguisher, could probably find one inside one of the houses."
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_OBJ_03"				"An open sewer with some type of gas leaking out of it, we'll need gas masks before we can enter."
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_OBJ_04"				"Heard the military had a temporary treatment centre in the park, probably worth heading over there and checking it out."
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_OBJ_05"				"Looks like some of these gates are locked, go figure. Probably a code somewhere in the park we need to open them."
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_OBJ_06"				"Found a code, hopefully it opens these interior gates that are still locked and functional."
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_OBJ_07"				"With these gas masks it is safe to enter the sewer we passed on the way here earlier."
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_OBJ_08"				"Make sure your gas mask is on before you enter, the gas down there is probably lethal."
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_OBJ_09"				"Can hardly see a damn thing down here. I guess just follow the trail of flares and see where it leads."
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_OBJ_10"				"Finally the end I think I can see daylight, let's get the hell out of here and hope wherever we are now is less shitty."
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_OBJ_11"				"Whoa I sure didn't expect to see something like this. Looks like a plantation, let's get inside and have a look around."
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_OBJ_12"				"Found a locked door in the hallway by the front door, must be some keys somewhere inside laying around."
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_OBJ_13"				"Got the locked door open. Searching the basement, probably a couple of clues down there for it to have been locked."
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_OBJ_14"				"Found a notepad down here that says garden maze code 3829. Also there's a key card reader down here in the basement."
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_OBJ_15"				"Got a key card, should be able to access the door in the basement now."
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_OBJ_16"				"Got the basement key card door open let's see where it leads."
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_OBJ_17"				"Oh... Another sewer... Great... On a positive note, at least this one isn't full of lethal gas."
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_OBJ_18"				"A way out of here, crossing my fingers it leads somewhere not full of zombies, toxic waste or burning dead bodies."
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_OBJ_19"				"It's the gas station by the park, let's take a look around and see what we can find. Looks like other survivors used to live here..."
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_OBJ_20"				"OK that does it both generators are running we should be able to call for extraction using the radio on the roof now."
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_OBJ_21"				"There's a radio on the roof! If we get all the generators started we can probably radio for evacuation!"
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_OBJ_22"				"Here comes the EVAC cut the lock off that gate and run for it!"
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_OBJ_23"				"Got the gate open let's go!"
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_OBJ_24"				"Damn, this checkpoint gate is locked. We can probably cut the lock off with some boltcutters."
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_OBJ_25"				"Nice got the gate open, let's keep checking houses on the way to the heart of the city for anything useful."
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_OBJ_26"				"Found some boltcutters, should probably hang onto these they might be useful."
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_OBJ_27"				"The alarm has locked the outer gates, we're trapped in here!. We have to hold out until the alarm clears and we can get out!"
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_OBJ_28"				"Hey a radio! Maybe we should try our luck and see if anyone is listening on the other end?"
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_OBJ_29"				"SHIT! There's something wrong with the generator and the alarms are attracting a bunch of zombies!"
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_OBJ_30"				"Found an armory with some weapons and ammo, if only we knew the code to open the door."
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_OBJ_31"				"Looks like the alarm has reset, make sure everyone grabbed a gas mask and let's head over to the sewer."
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_OBJ_32"				"What the hell set off that alarm! Shit there doesn't seem to be a way through, kill as many as you can!"
		"VSCRIPT_Montclair_OBJ_33"				"The zombies opened up a hole in that wall, let's see if there's a way through!"

		// RonaokePD
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_MapInit"				"Okay, we made it this far, now let's find some weapons and get out of here."
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_FoundBolters"		"I found the boltcutters."
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_FoundKeys"			"I found some keys, hopefully this will let us open some locked doors "
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_Basement"			"Let's head to the basement and look for a way out."
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_Roof"				"roof."		// Text Addition
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_Garage"				"garage."	// Text Addition
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_KeyCard"				"I found the keycard for the armory!"

		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_OBJ_00"				"This door at Guard Station 2 is locked, we need to find some keys."
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_OBJ_01"				"This door at Guard Station 1 is locked, I think we need to find some keys."
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_OBJ_02"				"I found the keys, follow me and I can open the door to Guard Station "
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_OBJ_03"				"The Guard Station is open, we need to activate the control panel for the Cell Block."
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_OBJ_03_C1"			"Guard Station 2 is open, we need to unlock the second guard door to proceed. It's the only way out."
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_OBJ_03_C2"			"The second Guard Station 2 door is now unlocked."
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_OBJ_04"				"I just activated the control panel, we need to head on through Cell Block "
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_OBJ_05"				"We need to head to Cell Block B, it's not far."
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_OBJ_06"				"The door to Cell Block B is closed, we need to find a way to open the door."
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_OBJ_07"				"Let's go to Guard Station 3, from there we should have access to other areas in this Cell Block."
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_OBJ_08"				"Loading dock secured, we can open up the offices now."
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_OBJ_09"				"It seems the alarm system has disabled the offices until the loading dock is closed."
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_OBJ_10"				"The offices are open, lets look for supplies then head on through."
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_OBJ_11"				"Okay, lets keep moving until we reach the main stairwell, then lets head to the "
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_OBJ_12"				"There is a large fire blocking our path, we need a Fire Extinguisher."
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_OBJ_13"				"The fire has been put out, lets head to the "
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_OBJ_14"				"There is a chain lock on these doors, there might be some boltcutters in the garage area."
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_OBJ_15"				"These doors are chained, the only way we're getting through is with some boltcutters. Let's check the roof."
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_OBJ_16"				"There should be a control panel close by for this door."
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_OBJ_17"				"Basement door opened, lets continue to the garage."
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_OBJ_18"				"I found an armory! Come and get weapons, ammo and supplies!"
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_OBJ_19"				"The doors to the roof are locked with a chain, we need to find some boltcutters."
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_OBJ_20"				"We should head to the radio tower and see if we can get extracted."
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_OBJ_21"				"The radio is broken. It was worth a try, let's head down to the basement garage instead."
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_OBJ_22"				"We should try the radio tower first before going to the basement."
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_OBJ_23"				"Looks like this door is blocked from the other side. We'll have to find another way down."
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_OBJ_24"				"We can jump down this elevator shaft, but try to land near the door below!"
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_OBJ_25"				"Let's continue through the offices and head to the basement."
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_OBJ_26"				"We now have access to the roof, let's head to the radio tower and try call for an extraction."
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_OBJ_27"				"The generator has been activated, we should now have access to the radio tower!"
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_OBJ_28"				"The chain has been cut, let's go through this maintenance area to the roof."
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_OBJ_29"				"I've cut the chain, let's head into the garage and find a vehicle to escape in!"
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_OBJ_30"				"The gate is opening now, it won't be long until we're out of here."
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_OBJ_31"				"Whoa, the power went out, we need to find the generator and activate it ASAP!"
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_OBJ_32"				"The Generator is back online, we need to activate the door again!"
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_OBJ_33"				"We need to activate the floodlights so the chopper knows where to land."
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_OBJ_34"				"The helipad floodlights have been activated, lets hold out until the chopper arrives!"
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_OBJ_35"				"The gate is opening, let's holdout until we can get past it and escape in that Hummer."
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_OBJ_36"				"The door to Cell Block B is open."
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_OBJ_37"				"You guys need to hurry. You have two minutes to get to the chopper or it will leave."
		"VSCRIPT_RoanokePD_OBJ_38"				"You have two minutes to get to the garage or we have to leave without you."

		// StoneCreek Valley
		"VSCRIPT_StoneCreekValley_ZombieInvasion"				"Zombies are closing in! Brace yourselves!"
		"VSCRIPT_StoneCreekValley_MapStart"						"We made it to Stone Creek Valley. But the road a head is blocked. We need to find another way around."
		"VSCRIPT_StoneCreekValley_EscapeFound_A"				"We are quite lucky, we found an army truck! Bad news is that it's out of gas."
		"VSCRIPT_StoneCreekValley_EscapeFound_B"				"It looks like they were in a hurry here. Let's check if we can find a {gold}gascan{white} and a {gold}hose{white} around here."
		"VSCRIPT_StoneCreekValley_Found_Hose"					"Found the {gold}hose{white} for the {gold}gascan{white}!"
		"VSCRIPT_StoneCreekValley_Found_GasCan"					"I found a {gold}gascan{white}!"
		"VSCRIPT_StoneCreekValley_GotBoth"						"Now that we got both, let's take the gas from our car and pour it into our gascan."
		"VSCRIPT_StoneCreekValley_GasGet01"						"The gascan is only {gold}half full{white}! We need to find some more gas."
		"VSCRIPT_StoneCreekValley_GasGet02"						"We got enough fuel for our gascan, let's head to the {gold}truck{white} so we can fill it up!"
		"VSCRIPT_StoneCreekValley_GasFuel"						"The truck has been filled up! Let's get out of here!"
		"VSCRIPT_StoneCreekValley_WeaponsLocker"				"There's a weapon stock here, we should locate the keys to get access."
		"VSCRIPT_StoneCreekValley_KeysObtained"					"We found the keys, now let's open the weapon stock room in the basement."
		"VSCRIPT_StoneCreekValley_DoorUnlocked"					"The door to the Weapon Stock is now unlocked!"
		"VSCRIPT_StoneCreekValley_GeneratorRunning"				"This generator sure is noisy! But we got the generator running, so let's call for help!"
		"VSCRIPT_StoneCreekValley_HouseReached"					"Looks like the people of this place didn't make it. Hopefully we may find something useful."
		"VSCRIPT_StoneCreekValley_BoltsNeeded"					"The gates are locked, we need some boltcutters to get trough."
		"VSCRIPT_StoneCreekValley_MilitaryPresence_A_0"			"Looks like the military has been here. But it looks like they didn't have enough time."
		"VSCRIPT_StoneCreekValley_MilitaryPresence_A_1"			"To get trough here, we require the code for the fence. We need to be careful as it may trip the alarm if we open the fence."
		"VSCRIPT_StoneCreekValley_MilitaryPresence_B"			"We got the keycode for this fence, but we need to be careful. Since the alarm may trip."
		"VSCRIPT_StoneCreekValley_GotKeyCode"					"Found the code for the fence!"
		"VSCRIPT_StoneCreekValley_AlarmTrip"					"We need to do this fast, before a horde of zombies shows up!"
		"VSCRIPT_StoneCreekValley_Notes0"						"Looks like there are more to the notepad, it explains that we need to find some {gold}gas{white} for the truck. They didn't get far it seems."
		"VSCRIPT_StoneCreekValley_Notes1"						"What we need are the following items:\n  {gold}Gascan\n  Hose"
		"VSCRIPT_StoneCreekValley_Notes2"						"It says that we can find them in 3 possible locations. {gold}1st House Basement{white}, {gold}2nd House Basement{white} or {gold}2nd House Garage{white}. There is also a possibilty that they forgot the {gold}gascan{white} near the {gold}escape vehicle{white}."
		"VSCRIPT_StoneCreekValley_Notes3"						"But we need a {gold}bolt cutter{white} to open up the front gates. We may find one in the {gold}Basement{white} or inside the {gold}Garage{white} of the {gold}2nd House{white}."

		// Last Stop (Part 1)
		"AS_LastStop_ArrivedToStation"							"We finally arrived to Union Station. The backup generator is still running, so that's a good sign..."
		"AS_LastStop_BeginMsg0"									"The train should still be at the station, since the {gold}main power{white} has been shut off manually."
		"AS_LastStop_BeginMsg1"									"So we need to first {gold}find a way to restart the power{white}, and then get out of there."
		"AS_LastStop_BeginMsg2"									"Of course, I doubt it's going to be that easy..."
		"AS_LastStop_BeginMsg3"									"First things first, let's head to the {gold}basement{white}, that's where the {green}generators{default} should be located at."
		"AS_LastStop_Escape"									"We need to get of here! This place is going to be crawling with zombies!"
		"AS_LastStop_RequiresKey"								"Looks like we need a set of keys to enter the basement..."
		"AS_LastStop_RequiresBolt"								"Looks like we need a boltcutter to get through here."
		"AS_LastStop_EscRouteBlocked"							"Looks like this lock is broken. We need to find another way..."
		"AS_LastStop_Pickup_KeyCard00"							"I found the {red}red{white} keycard!"
		"AS_LastStop_Pickup_KeyCard01"							"I found the {green}green{white} keycard!"
		"AS_LastStop_Pickup_KeyCard02"							"I found the {yellow}yellow{white} keycard!"
		"AS_LastStop_Pickup_Keys"								"I got the keys to the basement!"
		"AS_LastStop_Pickup_BoltCutter"							"I got the boltcutters! This will come in handy."
		"AS_LastStop_Pickup_Fuse"								"I found a fuse! This will come in handy."
		"AS_LastStop_EscapeAreaUnlocked"						"I've unlocked the path to our escape route."
		"AS_LastStop_NeedsPower"								"Crap. The power won't turn on... Looks like the fuses for this power box was removed manually."
		"AS_LastStop_PowerOn"									"It's going to take a little while before the power turns on. So let's head to the train!"
		"AS_LastStop_FusesPlaced"								"All fuses has been placed! Time to turn on the power."
		"AS_LastStop_FuseInserted"								" fuses left until we can turn on the power..."
		"AS_LastStop_AlarmTripped"								"Crap, the alarm got tripped. Now every damn zombie within the city will know where we are."
		"AS_LastStop_KeyReminder"								"We might find the keys from one of the security staff corpses."
		"AS_LastStop_BasementOpen"								"The basement is now open! Let's search where the powerbox is located at."
		"AS_LastStop_FuseBox"									"Found the power box, let's check if we can turn it on."
		"AS_LastStop_GreenDoorAlarm"							"I found where the main generator is at. It requires the {green}green {white}keycard, but the door is larmed."
		"AS_LastStop_GreenDoor"									"I found a door that requires the {green}green {white}keycard in the basement."
		"AS_LastStop_RedDoor1"									"The cafeteria door requires the {red}red {white}keycard."
		"AS_LastStop_RedDoor2"									"The closet in the 2nd floor requires the {red}red {white}keycard."
		"AS_LastStop_YellowDoor1"								"The security door at the {green}Station Master{white} requires the {yellow}yellow {white}keycard."
		"AS_LastStop_YellowDoor2"								"I found a door in the {green}Baggage Room{white} that requires a {yellow}yellow {white}keycard."
		"AS_LastStop_YellowDoor3"								"Found a door in the {green}Staff Offices{white} that requires the {yellow}yellow {white}keycard."
		"AS_LastStop_RoutePathA"								"We can get to the train trough the main entrance!"
		"AS_LastStop_RoutePathB"								"We can get to the train trough the outside of the cafeteria!"

		// Last Stop (Part 2)
		"AS_LastStop_Train_OnBoard"								"We finally got on the train... That sure wasn't easy, the whole Union Station got over run with zombies."
		"AS_LastStop_Train_Radio_Start"							"Let's turn on the radio, and listen in on the available channels..."
		"AS_LastStop_Train_Radio_0"								"You gotta be kidding me! The military will blow up the A-55 where this train will pass through!"
		"AS_LastStop_Train_Radio_1"								"We need to stop this train before that happens!"
		"AS_LastStop_Train_ZombiesOnTheTrain"					"Not only are there zombies on the train, but C4's! We gotta defuse them before they blow up."
		"AS_LastStop_Train_BombDefused_01"						"We got a C4 defused!"
		"AS_LastStop_Train_BombDefused_02"						" left."
		"AS_LastStop_Train_BombsDefused"						"We got all C4's defused! Let's stop this death train!"
		"AS_LastStop_Train_TimeRunningOut"						"Crap, the time is running out! We need to find all the C4's before we all get blown to bits!"
		"AS_LastStop_Train_Power_Needed"						"This door got no power, so it won't even budge no matter what we do. We need to find another way..."
		"AS_LastStop_Train_RequireExting"						"The diner wagon is on fire, and we need something to put out the fire with. There may be a Fire Extinguisher here somewhere."
		"AS_LastStop_Train_RequireBolting"						"Great. We need boltcutters to continue onwards..."
		"AS_LastStop_Train_Pickup_Exting"						"I've got the Fire Extinguisher! This will come in handy."
		"AS_LastStop_Train_Power1_On"							"Alright, the power box has been repaired. The power is back, so the doors should be unlocked."
		"AS_LastStop_Train_Power2_On"							"The last power box has been repaired, let's continue on!"
		"AS_LastStop_Train_RestorePower"						"We need to find another power box. This door won't open until the darn power is back."
		"AS_LastStop_Train_ReachedEnd"							"We finally reached to the end! Let's defuse the last remaining C4's and stop this god forsaken train from derailing!"

		// Last Stop (Part 3)
		"AS_LastStop_Forest_Start"							"We managed to stop the train before crashing into the collapsed A-55 tunnel. But now we now need to find another way towards {gold}Rowen's Dam{white}."
		"AS_LastStop_Forest_Office"							"Looks like this leads to the office section of this building. Maybe we can find a way out trough there?"
		"AS_LastStop_Forest_ToHighway"						"Our only way forwards is trough the highway."
		"AS_LastStop_Forest_HighwayBlocked"					"Well, looks like the highway plan failed before it even started. There must be a way out of here somewhere."
		"AS_LastStop_Forest_TrainWreck"						"One of the train cars went trough the highway sound barrier wall, maybe we can get trough there?"
		"AS_LastStop_Forest_HouseRescue"					"Looks like we ended up in someones backyard. And not only that, the basement is open. Let's take refuge in there!"
		"AS_LastStop_Forest_RequireKey"						"The door is locked, we need to find a {gold}set of keys{white} to open it."
		"AS_LastStop_Forest_KeyFound"						"Found a set of keys! With these, we can leave this building trough the {gold}side entrance{white}."
		"AS_LastStop_Forest_BridgeCross"					"A bridge! We should be able to cross it if we {gold}find a way to lower it{white}."
		"AS_LastStop_Forest_BridgePass"						"Now that we passed the bridge, let's continue on towards the dam!"
		"AS_LastStop_Forest_PanicEvent_Bridge"				"Well, that doesn't bode well. That alarm is going to attract every darn zombie in this whole area!"
		"AS_LastStop_Forest_BridgeLocked"					"Looks like the {gold}bridge control tower{white} requires a {lightgreen}green keycard{white}. We won't be able to {gold}lower the bridge{white} until we find one."
		"AS_LastStop_Forest_TyrtleParkingLot"				"The military was holding this section for awhile. But from the looks of things, it didn't end well. They left most of their equipment behind in a rush."
		"AS_LastStop_Forest_TyrtleMaintenence"				"Looks like we reached the end of the maintenance section. Let's look for the way out of here."
		"AS_LastStop_Forest_TunnelBlockade"					"The tunnel is blocked, just our luck... But it looks like there is another way trough that {gold}maintenance door{white}."
		"AS_LastStop_Forest_EerieRoad"						"Looks like the path lead us to a road! But it looks like things went south even from here."
		"AS_LastStop_Forest_YellowCardRequired"				"It looks like we require a yellow keycard to access the warehouse."
		"AS_LastStop_Forest_YellowCardFound"				"I've found the {yellow}Yellow Card{white}! Now we will be able to access the warehouse!"
		"AS_LastStop_Forest_GreenCardFound"					"Found the {lightgreen}Green Keycard{white} for the {gold}control tower{white}! Now we just need to get back to the {green}bridge{white}."
		"AS_LastStop_Forest_KeyCodeMaintFound"				"I've found the code for the bridge {gold}maintenance area{white}!"
		"AS_LastStop_Forest_KeyCodeRequired"				"Looks like we need a code to access the {gold}maintenance area{white} under the {green}bridge{white}."
		"AS_LastStop_Forest_MainAccess"						"The {gold}maintenance area{white} under the {green}bridge{white} is now open, let's continue on wards!"
		"AS_LastStop_Forest_MainPathBlocked"				"It's barricaded from the other side. We have to find another way around."
		"AS_LastStop_Forest_PanicEvent_Gate"				"The warehouse is open for business, but so are the zombies! Let's stick together!"
		"AS_LastStop_Forest_ShipWreckage"					"This is one hell of a wreckage. We should be able to pass trough here by using the debris."
		"AS_LastStop_Forest_BridgeWorkArea"					"Seems like this section of the bridge was under some kind of repair."
		"AS_LastStop_Forest_SidePath"						"Looks like we weren't the only ones coming trough here. There is even a boat up ahead, but from the looks of it, it made quite the mess."
		"AS_LastStop_Forest_SideGate"						"This path leads us down to the river. Maybe we can find {gold}something useful{white} down there."
		"AS_LastStop_Forest_PowerIsOff"						"Looks like the power has been turned off. It's looks like everything is currently running on backup power. Let's find and turn on the generators!"
		"AS_LastStop_Forest_MainGenerator"					"Only the main generator left! It should be in the main {gold}generator room{white}."
		"AS_LastStop_Forest_GeneratorOn"					"And the power is on, the keypad should now work!"
		
		// 0 - Keys
		"AS_LastStop_Forest_TipMsg0-0"							"We may find a way out of here by going trough the {gold}side entrance{white}. But that door requires a set of keys."
		"AS_LastStop_Forest_TipMsg0-1"							"The keys should be on the {gold}first floor{white}. We can find a set of stairs to the offices if we follow the large hallway down."
		// 1 - Yellow KeyCard
		"AS_LastStop_Forest_TipMsg1-0"							"We may find the keycard if we look around in the surrounding area."
		"AS_LastStop_Forest_TipMsg1-1"							"Maybe it's in one of the {gold}medical tents{white}, or perhaps {gold}under the bridge{white}."
		// 2 - KeyCode
		"AS_LastStop_Forest_TipMsg2-0"							"I heard that there is a {gold}warehouse{white} in this area somewhere. Maybe the code can be found there?"
		"AS_LastStop_Forest_TipMsg2-1"							"We can probably find the keycode for {gold}maintenance area{white} under the {green}bridge{white} somewhere inside the {gold}warehouse{white}."
	}
}